<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Magical XMPP Service</title>
    <link>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Magical XMPP Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 18:34:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 18:34:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Impressum: Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG:
Nico Wellpott Scheideweg 157 26127 Oldenburg
Kontakt: Telefon: 0441 93652965
E-Mail:admin@magicbroccoli.de
Verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs. 2 RStV: Nico Wellpott
Haftungsausschluss (Disclaimer) Haftung für Inhalte Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich. Nach §§ 8 bis 10 TMG sind wir als Diensteanbieter jedoch nicht verpflichtet, übermittelte oder gespeicherte fremde Informationen zu überwachen oder nach Umständen zu forschen, die auf eine rechtswidrige Tätigkeit hinweisen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Statement</title>
      <link>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 18:34:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy The use of our website is usually possible without providing personal information. As far as possible the need for personal data (eg name, address or e-mail address) is voluntary. The provided data will not be shared without your express consent.
We point out that data transmission over the Internet (eg when communicating by e-mail) may have security gaps. A complete protection of data against access by third parties is not possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/termsofuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 18:34:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xmpp.magicbroccoli.de/post/termsofuse/</guid>
      <description>Registration and use of the service is free of charge. Users, who were more than 12 months inactive will be deleted automatically. unused accounts will be deleted after 30 days. Advertising within the network (product advertising, spam, etc.) is prohibited. The excessive use of the services ((Syn-) Flooding, etc.) and thus their impairment is prohibited. Actions that advance against the laws of the Federal Republic of Germany are prohibited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>